## Moulik Chaturvedi

(Software Developer)

CONTACT:

moulik.chaturvedi26@gmail.com

+91-8005060991

**WEBSITE:** 

https://moulik-portfolio.web.app/

LINKED IN:

www.linkedin.com/in/moulikchaturvedi

Profile

Experienced Software Developer with great designing skills and exceptionally good quality of projects in the fields of Artificial Intelligence, Cyber Security, Web Development, Mobile App Development and UI/UX Designing. I'm a bilingual and speak English and Hindi proficiently. I like spending my time Coding, playing Basket Ball/Table Tennis or by playing an instrument like my Guitar!

Experience

Developer, Lamarr Tech; Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh - 2021-Present

Created and delivered 10+ projects under 1 month. Helped clients increase customer retention by providing specialized real world algorithms to help their business.

Developer, Paravijjiyan LLP; Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh - 2020-Present

Designed cross platform applications. Worked on increasing the SEO score for several websites. Learned to reduce costs and improve scalability by using serverless architecture.

Lead Developer, MLAI; Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh - 2018-2020

Worked on one of a kind Artificial Intelligence powered projects. Worked on the code and interior designs of machines fueled with cutting edge technologies. Worked as the lead presenter in all the technical presentations including one at IIT, Kanpur.

Education

Jaypee University of Information Technology; Shimla, Himachal Pradesh - B.Tech, 2024 Sheiling House School; Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh - High School, 2020

Skills

I'm proficient at HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JAVA, C, PYTHON and MOBILE APP DEVELOPMENT.